<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="rssStyleSheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<!-- explanation of some things:
the description looks weird because I want to not destroy its readability when converting with xls -->
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <ttl>20000</ttl>
    <ns0:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>RSS Feed</title>
    <description>This is the description of your RSS feed</description>
    <link>https:kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org</link>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:28:52 CST</pubDate>
      <title>⩩⽨⾉.Ⅱ⚈⢈.⢏.1</title>
      <description>
This is just a little update. I did a little optimizing and added a new microblog post.
Changelog:
-added new microblog Post
-removed filter on home page for optimization
-vaguely started my Inside Mari shrine
-other stuff I've probably forgotten about
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:27:10 CST</pubDate>
      <title>⩩⽨⾉.Ⅱ⚈⢈.⢏</title>
      <description>
Two updates in one day :O I added a mailbox tab thats a guestbook if you want to say hello ^o^ and added some text and test results to the webmistress tab :)
Changelog:
-added mailbox link using atabook
-added new text in webmistress tab for favorite media
-added new marquee in webmistress tab for test results
-added some js files for a future project 0_o
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:34:10 CST</pubDate>
      <title>☨⧣⦎.ⷓ⶿➋ⷵ.Ⱌ hotfix</title>
      <description>
Changelog:
-optimized home page
-fixed horizontal bar
-switched css animation for horizontal bar with a marquee
-added new screenshot to site progress page
-made the site progress a bit better
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:22:10 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Version: ☨⧣⦎.ⷓ⶿➋ⷵ.Ⱌ</title>
      <description>
This is a pretty basic update. I just changed the borders around boxes a bit, changed the background image, and added a microblog post
Changelog:
-made rainbow bar around boxes skinnier and sharped the corners of the box
-changed background image to a tileable gradient cloud thing I made
-a few new microblog posts
-fixed weird styling bug on the changelog on the home page
-added a website progress thing with a gif of screenshots of the website
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 11:30:35 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Update Version: ⶼ⩛⋃.❈⠮ₚ.⍠</title>
      <description>
I actually wanted to wait a little bit to push this to my site until it was *done* whatever that means.
But I kind of hate seeing my old site when I know a slightly prettier version of it exists. Here is that version. Added a new about/webmistress tab and some fancy css animations
for clicking on them you can find it in the new site contents box. I'm a little worried too many css animation makes my site look template-y or hurts that neo-web 1.0 aesthetic
so I might chill on that for now.
Changelog:
-completely redid site contents box adding new pages that are desplayed in the center box
-added new css animations to site contents box
-aded webmistress page
-1 new microblog post
-changed some headings and stuff on pages
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 03:16:25 CST</pubDate>
      <title>New microblog Post
      </title> 
      <description>
        tiny little update about things :)
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:45:25 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Big update
        Version: 4.aQ!.C*jPX.1
      </title> 
      <description>
Changelog:
-added some blog styling
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 8 Apr 2025 18:01:30 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Big update
Version: 4.aQ!.C*jPX
      </title>
      <description>
        I added a japanese translation of the main page, added a new microblog post, a site news box, a preview of the microblog, and other stuff I have probably forgotten about.
Changelog:
-added japanese verison of homepage via json and javscript and IDs
-added a Site news box
-added a shrine page for later
-added a preview of the microblog below the main page
-other stuff i've probably forgotten about
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Thu, 3 Apr 2025 19:10:12 CST</pubDate>
      <title>medium to big update
Version: 2.Pm3.OsTSEw
      </title>
      <description>
        I changed the background for performance reasons. Also now that there are opaque boxes it's kind of pointless to have an animation in the back you can't see. I changed the bottom banner to CSS but improved it. There's a new microblog post, and I added a little video player that you can click to play a music snippet I made recently :3
Changelog:
-rewrote about section
-added actual local comic sans tff for compatibility
-added back buttons to alternative pages idk how I didn't have that before
-added basic responsive design for microblog and blog
-added trans flag button
-added crosstile background
-got rid of marquee in favor of css
-microblog post about serum present :3
-added new music snippet video player
-added new music snippet
-other stuff i've probably forgotten
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:12:32 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Microblog 
Version: Lb7.WVx.2qV</title>
      <description>
        I wanted to add a little microblog thing for me to talk about small little things and thoughts I have, and I found https://aegi.neocities.org/ and I just loved her site and blog and it finally pushed me to make one. Please check her site out. It's really cool B)
Changelog:
-added a microblog and a tiny amount of formatting.
-reverted much of the blog css I accidentally pushed oops and also added minimal formatting so its at least readable now
-cleaned out a bunch of unused or old files in my neocities
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:08:45 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Small update 
Version:!B.7xu.dnS.2</title>
      <description>small update to just clean things up
Changelog:
-replaced gross css animation with a much prettier js animation that replicates marquee
        -HAHAHA just kidding that broke instantly on pushing I just switched it to marquee bad webdev practices yada yada yada whatever
-changed about paragraph and picture
-added some new buttons and a new site I like by winteryear! seriously they are so cool check them out by clicking the button :D
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:31:52 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Small update 
Version:!B.7xu.dnS.1</title>
      <description>small update to fix a few things
Changelog:
-fixed title not loading correctly on some resolutions
-changed font size for p to better format about container
-changed image from yui to a picture I took. I'm not sure I like it but we will see
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:17:52 CST</pubDate>
      <title>Changing Formatting 
Version:!B.7xu.dnS</title>
      <description> I changed TONSSS of formatting in this one :D it looks so much prettier. ALSO, I added responsive design finally lol so it works on phones. There are probably issues but it seems to work okay on most phones. I also made and added a daft punk button to the horizontally scrolling buttons.
Changelog:
-added responsive design
-changed Title and big header
-made rss feed prettier
-completely reworked the containers and boxes
-added daftpunk button
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 01:29:35 CST</pubDate>
      <title> A hot fix... sort of 
version: Ì.𝚭.Ⴢ.§</title>
      <description> In my last push I kind of destroyed my RSS widget. I just couldn't stand for that it really killed me lol. So I spent a ton of time... hours... figuring out how to write my own rss widget. I was trying to use javascript like a noob. I didn't know xlst existed to auto format xml its so awesome THANK YOU W3. This isn't a hotfix in that its small and meant to fix things. It fixes things by changing a lot so its like a regular smallish update done "hot"-ly I guess.
Changelog:
-changed font to trebuchet (tbh the pixely one was getting obnoxious, it isn't websafe or standard so it was so hard to use with xls, and most importantly IT WAS DESTROYING MY KAOMOJIs :((( so I just decided to change it. I had meant to do this anyway)
-removed php rss widget
-created XLS to format XML and display in an object element
-I think thats it
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 10:17:20 CST</pubDate>
      <title> Finally back Medium size update 
Version: Ì.𝚭.Ⴢ</title>
      <description> The biggest changes were a new music box on the left, removing the scrolling images box I had to make room for future plans >:), a new blog post about my recent experiences finding my voice in my music, and A DOMAIN NAME YAY ٩(^ᗜ^ )و. Also a new blog post :). I was heavily inspired by doqmeat for the music box so thank you to them :). You can find their website in my buttons box :D
Changelog:
-changed margin sizes in index
-removed scrolling images
-change domain name
-added box for music i've most recently listened to
-got rid of weird rss item add python script i'm just going to add it manually to preserve line breaks
-New blog post about Finding my Voice in my music :)
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Mar 2025 23:55:35 CST</pubDate>
      <title>New Background</title>
      <description>I have finally added a different background :D the old one was quite slow and a bit too much. This visual was made in p5js! I designed it kind of inspired by https://ramcst.neocities.org/ please check him out! its a really cool site. I initially loaded p5js but there were tons of rendering issues and it was very resource intensive. I refined it a lot and then just took a video of it and put that in the site instead :P so no p5js is running. Imagine my shock when I d for free accounts :( after all that work :((( so I just caved and got supporter c: i love neocities anyways I am happy to support. Let me know if this background is a lot overstimulating lol. I ha ve a lot of exams next week so I have to ban myself from working on this for a week or two :( its just insanely distracting I will sink so many hours into :/ Also I am really starting to realize the limitations of just manually pushing using CLI from a local directory so I might switch to github. I also started using visual studio. HUGE quality of life thing for sure. That's all! I hope this update finds you well! ^_^</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 3 Mar 2025 12:05:33 CST</pubDate>
      <title>New Blog Post (My Experience with Vyvanse)</title>
      <description>I post about my experience with my new medication, Vyvanse, and a little, hopefully understandable explanation of how it works in the brain :)</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/blog/posts/2025-03-03-my-experience-with-vyvanse.md</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:59:32 CST</pubDate>
      <title>MY BLOG IS LIVE!</title>
      <description>I have finished building the way my blog works outside of sytling and have put it up. Obviously it has no styling right now, but I'll fix that later this was a hassle enough even though it really doesn't look like much lol</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/blog.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:31:15 CST</pubDate>
      <title>RSS Button</title>
      <description>I put a button in the changelog box that links to my RSS xml (^_^)</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:11 CST</pubDate>
      <title>RSS Widget Added</title>
      <description>Okay I implemented it basically instantly. Javascript is far too slow at working with html. I have used a widget generator to make one for me in php which is nice. However... I wasted like 4 hours of life（；¬＿¬). Unfortunately neocities can't host php files so I have to hotlink and it might break later but oh well. Hopefully it all works now.</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:11:26 CST</pubDate>
      <title>FINALLY I ADDED RSS</title>
      <description>This was one of if not the hardest thingsgs I have ever coded. RSS is actually fairly easy to implement.I don't have supporter so I had to come up with some work around where I could manually push to neocities from local files. For some reason, after this I decided to basically build my own rss widget in javascript and it was insanely hard to put it lightly. I spent 4 hours and it barely works and I still need to implement it on the website. I'm considering making a tutorial for all of this because I had to go to 100 different resources just to figure it out. ANYWAYS thats all ^-^</description>
      <link>https://akibaten.xyz/test.html</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>