<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="rssStyleSheet.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<!-- explanation of some things:
the description looks weird because I want to not destroy its readability when converting with xls -->
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <ttl>20000</ttl>
    <ns0:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <title>RSS Feed</title>
    <description>This is the description of your RSS feed</description>
    <link>https:kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org</link>
    <item>
      <pubDate> Mon, 24 Mar 2025 10:17:20 CST</pubDate>
      <title> Finally back Medium size update Version: Ì.𝚭.Ⴢ</title>
      <description> The biggest changes were a new music box on the left, removing the scrolling images box I had to make room for future plans >:), a new blog post about my recent experiences finding my voice in my music, and A DOMAIN NAME YAY ٩(^ᗜ^ )و. Also a new blog post :). I was heavily inspired by doqmeat for the music box so thank you to them :). You can find their website in my buttons box :D
Changelog:
-changed margin sizes in index
-removed scrolling images
-change domain name
-added box for music i've most recently listened to
-got rid of weird rss item add python script i'm just going to add it manualy to preserve line breaks
-New blog post about Finding my Voice in my music :)
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Mar 2025 23:55:35 CST</pubDate>
      <title>New Background</title>
      <description>I have finally added a different background :D the old one was quite slow and a bit too much. This visual was made in p5js! I designed it kind of inspired by https://ramcst.neocities.org/ please check him out! its a really cool site. I initially loaded p5js but there were tons of rendering issues and it was very resource intensive. I refined it a lot and then just took a video of it and put that in the site instead :P so no p5js is running. Imagine my shock when I d for free accounts :( after all that work :((( so I just caved and got supporter c: i love neocities anyways I am happy to support. Let me know if this background is a lot overstimulating lol. I ha ve a lot of exams next week so I have to ban myself from working on this for a week or two :( its just insanely distracting I will sink so many hours into :/ Also I am really starting to realize the limitations of just manually pushing using CLI from a local directory so I might switch to github. I also started using visual studio. HUGE quality of life thing for sure. That's all! I hope this update finds you well! ^_^</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 3 Mar 2025 12:05:33 CST</pubDate>
      <title>New Blog Post (My Experience with Vyvanse)</title>
      <description>I post about my experience with my new medication, Vyvanse, and a little, hopefully understandable explanation of how it works in the brain :)</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/blog/posts/2025-03-03-my-experience-with-vyvanse.md</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:59:32 CST</pubDate>
      <title>MY BLOG IS LIVE!</title>
      <description>I have finished building the way my blog workss outside of sytling and have put it up. Obviously it has no styling right now, but I'll fix that later this was a hassle enough even though it really doesn't look like much lol</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/blog.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:31:15 CST</pubDate>
      <title>RSS Button</title>
      <description>I put a button in the changelog box that links to my RSS xml (^_^)</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:11 CST</pubDate>
      <title>RSS Widget Added</title>
      <description>Okay I implemented it basically instantly. Javascript is far too slow at working with html. I have used a widget generator to make one for me in php which is nice. However... I wasted like 4 hours of life（；¬＿¬). Unfortunately neocities can't host php files so I have to hotlink and it might break later but oh well. Hopefully it all works now.</description>
      <link>https://kingdomofakibaten.neocities.org/index.html</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:11:26 CST</pubDate>
      <title>FINALLY I ADDED RSS</title>
      <description>This was one of if not the hardest thingsgs I have ever coded. RSS is actually fairly easy to implement. I fdon't have supporter so I had to come up with some work arounds where I could manually push to neocities from local files. For some reason, after this I decided to basically build my own rss widget in javascript and it was insanely hard to put it lightly. I spent 4 hours and it barely works and I still need to implement it on the websitite. I'm considering making a tutorial for all of this because I had to go to 100 different resources just to figure it out. ANYWAYS thats all ^-^</description>
      <link>https://akibaten.xyz/test.html</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>